passionshop.com 2019-06-12

# Privacy Statement | PassionShop

DRS, Inc. / Passionshop.com is a licensee of the TRUSTe Privacy Program. TRUSTe is an independent organization whose mission is to enable individuals and organizations to establish trusting relationships based on respect for personal identity and information by promoting the use of fair information practices. This privacy statement covers the site www.passionshop.com. Because this Web site wants to demonstrate its commitment to our users. privacy, it has agreed to disclose its information practices and have its privacy practices reviewed for compliance by TRUSTe. If you have questions or concerns regarding this statement, you should first contact [service@passionshop.com](mailto:service@passionshop.com). 

If you do not receive acknowledgement of your inquiry or your inquiry has not been satisfactorily addressed, you should contact TRUSTe at <http://www.truste.org/consumers/watchdog_complaint.php> TRUSTe will then serve as a liaison with us to resolve your concerns. 

By displaying the TRUSTe trustmark, passionshop.com has agreed to notify users of: 

**Registration**  
In order to use this Web site, you must first complete the registration form and create a user name and password. During registration you are required to give contact information (such as name and email address). We use this information to contact you about the services on our site in which you have expressed interest. 

DRS, Inc. is the sole owner of the information collected on passionshop.com. DRS, Inc. collects personally identifiable information from our users at several different points on our Web site. 

**Application Forms**  
If you purchase a service requiring financial information on our site, we require that you provide certain personally identifiable information, including your name, address, phone number and credit card number. This information is necessary to process your order. 

**Newsletters**  
If you wish to subscribe to our newsletter(s), we will use your name and email address to send the newsletter to you. Out of respect for your privacy, we provide you a way to unsubscribe. Please see the .Choice and Opt-out. section. 

**Service-related Announcements**  
We will send you strictly service-related announcements on rare occasions when it is necessary to do so. For instance, if our service is temporarily suspended for maintenance, we might send you an email. 

**Profile**  
We store information that we collect through cookies, log files, clear gifs, and third party sources to create a .profile. of your preferences. We tie your personally identifiable information, and your purchasing history, to information in the profile, in order to provide tailored promotions and marketing offers and to improve the content of the site for you. 

We do not share your profile or personal information with other third parties for promotional use. 

**Service Providers**  
We use an outside shipping company to fulfill orders, and a credit card processing company to bill you for goods and services. These companies do not retain, share, store or use personally identifiable information for any other purposes. 

We use other third parties to provide streaming video (Video on Demand) on our site. When you sign up for streaming video (Video on Demand), we will share your user id as necessary for the third party to provide that service. 

These third parties are not given your personally identifiable information for any purpose. 

**Legal Disclaimer**  
We reserve the right to disclose your personally identifiable information as required by law and when we believe that disclosure is necessary to protect our rights and/or to comply with a judicial proceeding, court order, or legal process served on our Web site 

**Choice/Opt-out**  
If you purchase a product/service you will not receive any additional marketing material from us unless you select to subscribe to our newsletter. 

If you no longer wish to receive our newsletter and promotional communications, you may opt-out of receiving them by following the instructions included in each newsletter or communication or by emailing us at [service@passionshop.com](mailto:service@passionshop.com)

**Cookies**  
A cookie is a small text file that is stored on a user.s computer for record-keeping purposes. We use cookies on this site. We do not link the information we store in cookies to any personally identifiable information you submit while on our site. 

We use both session ID cookies and persistent cookies. We use session cookies to make it easier for you to navigate our site and to remember items placed in your shopping cart. A session ID cookie expires when you close you browser. A persistent cookie remains on your hard drive for an extended period of time. You can remove persistent cookies by following directions provided in your Internet browser.s .help. file. <http://support.microsoft.com/kb/278835>

We set a persistent cookie to store your passwords, so you don.t have to enter it more than once. Persistent cookies also enable us to track and target the interests of our users to enhance the experience on our site. 

If you reject cookies, you may still use our site, but with cookies the contents of your shopping cart can be held for longer periods of time allowing you to resume shopping at a later date. 

Some of our business partners (e.g., advertisers) use cookies on our site. We have no access to or control over these cookies. See "Third Party Advertisers". 

This privacy statement covers the use of cookies by passionshop.com only and does not cover the use of cookies by any advertisers. 

**Links to Other Sites**  
This Web site contains links to other sites that are not owned or controlled by DRS, Inc. Please be aware that we, DRS, Inc, are not responsible for the privacy practices of such other sites. 

We encourage you to be aware when you leave our site and to read the privacy statements of each and every Web site that collects personally identifiable information. 

This privacy statement applies only to information collected by this Web site. 

**Access to Personally Identifiable Information**  
If your personally identifiable information changes, or if you no longer desire our service, you may correct, update, delete or deactivate it by making the change on our member information page or by emailing our Customer Support at [service@passionshop.com](mailto:service@passionshop.com) or by contacting us by telephone or postal mail at the contact information listed below. 

**Security**  
The security of your personal information is important to us. When you enter sensitive information (such as credit card number and/or social security number) on our registration or order forms, we encrypt that information using secure socket layer technology (SSL). To learn more about SSL, follow this link <http://www.verisign.com/ssl/ssl-information-center/how-ssl-security-works/index.html>

We follow generally accepted industry standards to protect the personal information submitted to us, both during transmission and once we receive it. No method of transmission over the Internet, or method of electronic storage, is 100% secure, however. Therefore, while we strive to use commercially acceptable means to protect your personal information, we cannot guarantee its absolute security. 

If you have any questions about security on our Web site, you can send email us at [service@passionshop.com](mailto:service@passionshop.com)

**Changes in this Privacy Statement**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes to this privacy statement, the page, and other places we deem appropriate so that you are aware of what information we collect, how we use it, and under what circumstances, if any, we disclose it. 

We reserve the right to modify this privacy statement at any time, so please review it frequently. If we make material changes to this policy, we will notify you here, by email, or by means of a notice on our home page. 

DRS, Inc.  
2600 SE Miami St  
Stuart, FL 34997 

Effective date 2.13.09
